What's up, guys? On today's video, we're
reviewing a
triangle helmet.
Came in this box. It is black. It is a
size medium. It has some vent holes here
and some vent holes down here. I took
off the visor just now because it was
the dark one. It came with a tinted
visor and also a clear visor. So, I'll
be putting that one on.
And you can see here, this is how where
you put the visor in. This little thing
here pushes back and it like opens up a
little bit so you can put it in there.
Move around to the back. The back looks
nice. Uh it's not too bulky.
Actually, it looks a little smaller.
It's not too wide. Looks good. Nice
round. And little uh design here. You
can see it's a medium.
ID number is TFF 15 FMVSS
218.
When we look inside, it has a nice good
padding here. It's a little hard to get
your head in here at first, but then the
padding opens up on the inside. Fits
pretty good. And then here's the buckle.
I believe these paddings are
um removable and you can add different
size paddings to make it fit more
comfortable on your head.
But yeah, this is the helmet.
So cool.